<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<AllNews default_image_thumb1="media/images/commons/logo1.png" default_image_thumb2="media/images/commons/generic1.png" default_image="media/images/commons/generic1.png">
	<NewsItem>
		<title>CSSA hosts Chinese Cultural Festival - 25 September</title>
		<image></image>
		<image_thumb></image_thumb>
		<name>chinese-cultural-event</name>
		<posting_date>09/21/2011</posting_date>
		<expire_date>10/21/2012</expire_date>
		<highlight>
			The Chinese Student and Scholar Associations of the D.C. metropolitan area are holding their Chinese Culture Festival this Sunday, Sept. 25.
		</highlight>
		<content>
		<![CDATA[
			<p>The Chinese Student and Scholar Associations of the D.C. metropolitan area are holding their Chinese Culture Festival this Sunday, Sept. 25.<br />
			<br />All university students, faculty members, and their families and friends are welcome.
			<br /><b>You do not need to be Chinese or speak Chinese to attend this event.</b> Admission is free. There will be games, prizes, and a raffle!</i><br />
			<br />Special guests include: <b>President Wallace Loh, Officials from the Chinese Embassy and business sponsors</b>.</p>
			<p><b>Festival Schedule:</b><br />
				11:00am - 5:00pm -  Exhibition @ Grand Ballroom, Stamp Student Union, University of Maryland - College Park <br />
				6:30pm - 9:00pm - Performance @ Dekelboum Concert Hall, Clarice Smith Performing Arts Center, University of Maryland - College Park</p>
				<p>The exhibition will showcase Chinese tea culture, traditional clothing, calligraphy, folk music and instruments, sports, Kung Fu, garden landscaping, Confucian philosophy, etc. Desserts and souvenirs will be for sale at the event.<br />
				The night performance will showcase dances, songs, Kung Fu, a magic show, and a fashion show.</p>
				<p><b>Pre-registration to the Chinese Cultural Festival is required.</b><br />
				For UMD students, faculty and staff, please register <a href="https://docs.google.com/spreadsheet/viewform?hl=en_US&formkey=dHRMbjgwQnU5a1pjZjU3cF9QOUFWblE6MQ#gid=0"><b>here</b></a>.<br />
				For people who are interested in this event outside of UMD, please register <a href="https://docs.google.com/spreadsheet/viewform?hl=en_US&formkey=dEgwWTZxWkpIUDY0aWJLQWYyNnp3b3c6MQ#gid=0"><b>here</b></a>.<br />
				Pre-registration is valid through Sept. 21 at 11:59pm. After your registration, there will be a confirmation email sent to you. Parking is available next to the venue. Please follow standard UMD parking lot assignments.</p>
				<p><b>Co-hosting Universities:</b><br />
				<i>
					University of Maryland, College Park<br />
					University of Virginia<br />
					Johns Hopkins University<br />
					Virginia Tech<br />
					University of Delaware<br />
					National Institute of Health<br /> 
					National Institute of Standards and Technology<br />
					National Institute of Health at Baltimore<br />
					Georgetown University<br />
					Virginia Commonwealth University<br />
					University of West Virginia<br />
					American University<br />
					George Mason University<br />
					George Washington University<br />
					Old Dominion University<br />
				</i>
				</p>
		]]>
		</content>
	</NewsItem>
	<NewsItem>
		<title>Library of Congress &amp; AALR 9/11 10th Anniversary Event</title>
		<image></image>
		<image_thumb></image_thumb>
		<name>aalr-911-anniversary-event</name>
		<posting_date>09/02/2011</posting_date>
		<expire_date>10/02/2012</expire_date>
		<highlight>
				The Library of Congress Asian Division and Asian American Pacific Islander Collection and The Asian American Literary Review are hosting an event to commemorate the 10th anniversary of 9/11.
		</highlight>
		<content>
		<![CDATA[
			<p>"September 11, 2011:  A Retrospective"</p>
			<p>The Library of Congress Asian Division and Asian American Pacific Islander Collection and The Asian American Literary Review are hosting an event to commemorate the 10th anniversary of 9/11, exploring specifically the legacies for South Asian, Muslim, and Arab Americans.</p>
			<p>The event will be held on Sept. 8, 1:00-2:30 pm at The Library of Congress Asian Reading Room.  Free to the public.  Performance and discussion.  Featuring some great speakers from the local community.</p>
			<p>Please see the program flyer for more details.</p>
		]]>
		</content>
	</NewsItem>
	<NewsItem>
		<title>Asian American Literary Review releases special issue commemorating tenth anniversary of Sept. 11</title>
		<image></image>
		<image_thumb></image_thumb>
		<name>aalr-press-release</name>
		<posting_date>08/16/2011</posting_date>
		<expire_date>10/21/2012</expire_date>
		<highlight>
			A critical consideration of the moment and its aftermath - the political, legal, and civil rights repercussions for the communities most directly affected: South Asian, Arab, Middle Eastern, and Muslim American.
		</highlight>
		<content>
		<![CDATA[
			<p>A critical consideration of the moment and its aftermath - the political, legal, and civil rights repercussions for the communities most directly affected: South Asian, Arab, Middle Eastern, and Muslim American.</p>
			<p>As the tenth anniversary of September 11th, 2001 approaches, how can we reflect on that day and its aftermath when so many of the voices of affected communities remain unheard? In the interests of broadening the public conversation, The Asian American Literary Review (AALR) is publishing a special commemorative issue that gives voice to those too frequently unheard.</p>
			<p>Special Guest reading and events are slated for early September.</p>
			<p style="text-align: right"><a href="http://www.aalrmag.org/issue3/september11.html">see more details</a></p>
		]]>
		</content>
	</NewsItem>
	<NewsItem>
		<title>AAST Offers New Courses</title>
		<image></image>
		<image_thumb></image_thumb>
		<name>newcourse</name>
		<posting_date>07/29/2011</posting_date>
		<expire_date>10/21/2012</expire_date>
		<highlight>
			AAST-498G and AAST-498K has been added to the Minor Program.
		</highlight>
		<content>
		<![CDATA[
			<p>Check <a href="http://www.sis.umd.edu/bin/soc?crs=aast&sec=&term=201108&starthour=12&startmin=00&ampm=am&level=All&center=0">Testudo</a> regularly to see updates on new courses and descriptions for AAST classes.
			<h3 style="text-decoration: underline; margin-top: 14px;">New to the Fall 2011 courselist:</h3>
			<b>AAST498G:</b> Asian American Women and Gender<br />
			<b>AAST498K:</b> Korean Americans: Culture and Society<br />
		]]>
		</content>
	</NewsItem>
	<NewsItem>
		<title>APALRC Seeks Interns for Fall 2011</title>
		<image></image>
		<image_thumb></image_thumb>
		<name>apalrc</name>
		<posting_date>07/28/2011</posting_date>
		<expire_date>10/21/2011</expire_date>
		<highlight>
			The Chinese Student and Scholar Associations of the D.C. metropolitan area are holding their Chinese Culture Festival this Sunday, Sept. 25.
		</highlight>
		<content>
		<![CDATA[
			<p>The Asian Pacific American Legal Resource Center (APALRC) is a 501(c) (3) community-based legal organization that works with low income and limited-English proficient Asian immigrant communities across the Washington D.C. metropolitan area.  The APALRC provides free legal assistance to low-income Asian immigrants who have limited English proficiency in a linguistically accessible and culturally appropriate manner.  It operates a multi-lingual legal intake helpline, a legal interpreter project, and provides legal assistance in immigration, domestic violence and family law, tenants' rights, and other areas.  The APALRC works to improve Asian Americans access to the legal system and to address the systemic inequities faced by Asian Americans and immigrants in our region.
			<p>For more details, <a href="/lib/downloads/Fall_2011_APALRC_Internship_Announcement.pdf" target="_blank">download the full announcement</a> or visit the <a href="http://www.apalrc.org" target="_blank">APALRC Website</a>.
		]]>
		</content>
	</NewsItem>
</AllNews>